Guide to the Cave Canem Records
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Audiovisual Material, 2002-2011; Series VI; 0.42; (1 box)
  - Program audio files- Legacy Conversations, readings, 2003-2005; 2; 6 audiocassettes (Box 28)
    - Lorenzo Thomas / Harryette Mullen (2 of 2), 2004 October 26; 1 (Box 28, Item barcode 39002091396912)
    - Conversation with Rita Dove & Elizabeth Alexander, NSU, original (1 of 2), 2003 October 2; 1 (Box 28, Item barcode 39002091396920)
    - Conversation with Rita Dove & Elizabeth Alexander, NSU, original (2 of 2), 2003 October 2; 1 (Box 28, Item barcode 39002091396938)
  - Fellows and faculty readings, 2011 June; 8 mini digital video cassettes (Box 28)
    - Faculty pt. #1: Hayes, Rankine, Phillips (1 of 2 miniDVs), 2011 June 20; 1 (Box 28, Item barcode 39002057145667)
    - Faculty pt. #2: Philips (2 of 2 miniDVs), 2011 June 20; 1 (Box 28, Item barcode 39002057145675)
    - Fellows Reading, part 1 of 2 (1 of 2 miniDVs), 2011 June 21; 1 (Box 28, Item barcode 39002057145600)
    - Fellows Reading, part 2 of 2 (2 of 2 miniDVs), 2011 June 21; 1 (Box 28, Item barcode 39002057145618)
    - Fellows Reading, part 1 of 2 (1 of 2 miniDVs), 2011 June 22; 1 (Box 28, Item barcode 39002057145642)
    - Fellows Reading, part 2 of 2 (2 of 2 miniDVs), 2011 June 22; 1 (Box 28, Item barcode 39002057145659)
    - Fellows Reading, part 1 of 2 (1 of 2 miniDVs), 2011 June 24; 1 (Box 28, Item barcode 39002057145634)
    - Fellows Reading, part 2 of 2 (2 of 2 miniDVs), 2011 June 24; 1 (Box 28, Item barcode 39002057145626)
- Restricted Material, Series VIII; 0.21; (1 box)
  Restricted until 2033 August 1. Consult the appropriate curator for further information.
  - Restricted files (Box 30)
    Box 30: Restricted until 2033 August 1. Consult the appropriate curator for further information.